A Guide to the Samuel Herrick Papers, 1930-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- SH numbered publications (see also listing in Box 1); numbered publications 62-110 (drafts, correspondence, reprints), 1950-1957. (Box 29)
  New elements and 1955 ephemeris of (1580) Betulia. (With W. P. Hirst and C. G. Hilton.) Minor Planet Circulars 1256, September 27, 1955.
  99
  Late 1955 ephemeris for object Wilson-Minkowski 1951RA. (With C. G. Hilton and G. L. Matlin.) Minor Planet Circulars 1280-1281, October 18, 1955.
  100
  1955-56 ephemerides of Jupiter's ninth and twelfth satellites. (With C. G. Hilton, G. L. Matlin, and Julie Bishin.) Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v. 67, pp. 421-422, December 1955.
  101
  1956 ten-day ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With C. G. Hilton.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1956, p. 7. 39. 50. 112. (Leningrad, 1955.)
  102
  Comet Haro-Chavira (1954 k.) (With Julie Bishin.) Harvard Annoucement Card 1326, April 3, 1956.
  103
  1956 ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With C. G. Hilton.) Minor Planet Circulars 1431-1432, June 1, 1956.
  104
  Elements and 1957 ten-day ephemerides of (1566) Icarus and (1580) Betulia. (With W. P. Hirst and C. G. Hilton.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1957, pp. 7, 41, 53, 117, 144. (Leningrad, 1956.)
  105
  Wirtanen object (1948 OA). (With C. G. Hilton.) Harvard Announcement Card 1333, August 13, 1956; extended in Minor Planet Circulars 1588, April 29, 1957.
  106
  Units and constants for geocentric orbits. (With R. M. L. Baker and C. G. Hilton.) Mimeographed by Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory, Cambridge, January 1957.
  107
  1957 ephemerides of Jupiter's ninth and twelfth satellites. (With C. G. Hilton.) Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v. 69, pp. 85-86, February 1957.
  108
  Final Report on Project D. (With eight others.) Systems Laboratories Corp., April 29, 1957. (Secret.)
  109
  1957 ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With C. G. Hilton.) Harvard Announcement Card 1360, May 23, 1957; Minor Planet Circulars 1593, May 22, 1957.
  110
  Formulae, Constants, Definitions, Notations for Geocentric and Heliocentric Orbits. Systems Laboratories Corporation, may 28, 1957. 31pp.
- SH numbered publications (see also listing in Box 1); numbered publications 111-129 (drafts, correspondence, reprints), 1957-1958. (Box 30)
  111
  Gravitational and related constants for accurate space navigation. (With R. M. L. Baker and C. G. Hilton.) Proceedings at the Eighth International Astronautical Congress, Barcelona, 1957, pp. 197-235 (Wein 1958); U.C.L.A. Astronomical Papers, v. 1, No. 24, pp. 297-338; Preprint by American Rocket Society No. 497-457, October 6, 1957. (Revision No. 106.)
  112
  Elements and 1958 ten-day ephemerides of (1566) Icarus, (1580) Betulia, (1620) Geographos. (with W. P. Hirst, C. G. Hilton, Silvia Marcus.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1958, pp. 9, 43, 44, 56, 112, 144, 153. (Leningrad, 1957.)
  113
  1957 Ephemeris of (1580) Betulia. (With W. P. Hirst and C. G. Hilton.) Minor Planet Circulars 1663, November 19, 1957.
  114
  Early 1958 ephemeris of (1620) Geographos. (With C. G. Hilton.) Minor Planet Circulars 1679, January 2, 1958.
  115
  Earth satellites and related orbit and perturbation theory. Space technology, Lecture 3A. University of California Extension Division (mimeographed, 12 pp.) January 27, 1958.
  116
  1958 ephemerides of Jupiter's ninth and twelfth satellites. (With C. G. Hilton.) Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v. 70, February 1958.
  117
  Icarus. (1958 ephemeris with C. G. Hilton and Silvia R. Marcus.) Harvard Announcement Card 1398-1399, March 3, 1958.
  118
  Trajectory fundementals. The Rand Corporation, P-1303. March 7, 1958.
  119
  1958 2-day ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With C. G. Hilton and Silvia R. Marcus.) Minor Planet Circulars 1703, March 7, 1958.
  120
  Orbits. (With R. M. L. Baker.) Aviation Age, March 1958, pp. 70-77.
  121
  Space navigation and the institute. Navigation, v. 6, pp. 3-4, Spring 1958.
  122
  Late 1958 ephemeris of (1620) Geographos. (With Charles G. Hilton and Silvia R. Marcus.) Minor Planet Circulars 1794, July 22, 1958.
  123
  Some aspects of aeronautics. (With R. W. Buchheim, E. H. Vestine, A. G. Wilson, ed. by P. Swerling.) The Rand Corporation, P-1442, July 23, 1958; I.R.E. Transactions on Military Electronics, MIL2, No. 1, pp. 8-19.
  124
  Astrodynamics. Chapters 1, 2, 4-9, 15. Glendale, Aeronautic Systems, Inc., August 4, 1958; 2nd ed. under expanded title: Notes on Astrodynamics and Rocket Navigation, Santa Monica, Douglas Aircraft Corp., November 25, 1958; 3rd ed., expanded title, San Diego, Convair Astronautics, December 1958; 4th ed., Astrodynamics, U.S.A.F., Edwards Air Force Base, March 1959; 5th ed., Autonetics Div., North American Aviation, Inc., July 1959; 6th ed., Douglas Aircraft Corp (2nd printing). October 1959; 7th ed., Jet Propulsion Lab, November 1959; 8th ed., Hughes Aircraft Co.,k February 11, 1960.
  125
  Coordinate systems of lunar vehicle orbits. (With C. G. Hilton.) Aeronutronic Publication U-245, August 8, 1958.
  126
  Recent advances in astrodynamics. (With R. M. L. Baker.) Jet Propulsion, 28, pp. 649-654, October 1958; U.C.L.A. Astronomical Papers, v. 2, No. 5, pp. 25-32.
  127
  A brief summary of orbit theory. (With Silvia R. Marcus.) The Rand Corporation, D-5543, September 2, 1958.
  128
  Ephemerides, representations, observational reference systems and data. Astrodynamics, Chapter 10. (Glendale, Aeronutronic Systems, Inc., November 1959.)
  129
  The status and improvement of physical constants neede for precision trajectories. The Rand Corporation, P-1559, December 1, 1958.
- SH numbered publications (see also listing in Box 1); numbered publications 130-138 (drafts, correspondence, reprints), 1959. (Box 31)
  130
  The influence of the earth's potential field on a nearly circular satellite. (With Louis G. Walters.) Aeronutronic Publication U-326, Janaury 9, 1959.
  131
  Space Handbook, Astronautics and its Applications. (With members of the Rand Corporation.) 85th Congress, 2nd Session. (United States Government Printing Office, Washington, 1959; 2nd ed., New York, Random House, 1959.)
  132
  Precision orbits and observation reduction. U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report, No. 1, June 11, 1959, AFOSR TN-5-769; Aeronutronic Publication U-386.
  133
  1959 ephemerides of Jupiter's ninth and twelfth satellites. (With C. G. Hilton.) Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v. 71, p. 172, April 1959.
  134
  Differential expressions for low eccentricity geocentric orbits. (With L. G. Walters and C. G. Hilton.) U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report, No. 2, June 11, 1959, AFOSR TN-59-768; Aeronutronic Publication U-456; Proceedings, Xth Astronautical Congress, 327-340. (Vienna, Springer-Verlag, 1960.)
  135
  Earth satellites and related orbit and perturbation theory. Space Technology (ed. H. A. Seiffert; New York, McGraw-Hill, 1959), pp. 5-01--5-30.
  136
  Differential representations, corrections and error analyses, Astrodynamics, Chapter 14. (Newport Beach, Aeronutronic, June 1959.)
  137
  The variation of parameters. Astrodynamics, Chapter 17. (Newport Beach, Aeronutronic, September 1959.); U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report No. 9, July 1960, 74 pp.
  138
  Astronomy session (Chairman). Proceedings. Lunar and Planetary Exploration Colloquium, v. 2, No. 1, pp. 34-48, September 23-24, 1959.
- SH numbered publications (see also listing in Box 1); numbered publications 139-169 (drafts, correspondence, reprints), 1959-1963. (Box 32)
  139
  "The astronomical unit" and the solar parallax. (With G. B. Westrom and Maud W. Makemson.) U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report No. 5, September 30, 1959, AFOSRTN 59-1044; Appendex G, Aeronutronic Publication U.583, September 28, 1959.
  140
  Astrodynamics: state of the art, 1959. (With R. M. L. Baker, Jr.) Astronautics, 4, No. 11, 30, 180, 181, November 1959; U.C.L.A. Astronomical Papers, v. 2, No. 6, pp. 33-36, 1959.
  141
  Elements of (1566) Icarus, (1580) Betulia, and (1620) Geographos. (With C. G. Hilton and W. P. Hirst.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1960. (Leningrad, 1959.)
  142
  1960 ephemerides of Jupiter's ninth and twelfth satellites. (With T. O. Montgomery.) Harvard Announcement Card 1478, April 14, 1960. Authors acknowledged on Harvard Annoucement Card 1480. Also Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 72, pp. 131-132, April 1960.
  143
  Position-and-velocity orbits from incomplete observations. Astrodynamics, Chapter 13. (Newport Beach, Aeronutronic, April 1960.)
  144
  Orbits from several incomplete position observations. Astrodynamics, Chapter 13. (Newport Beach, Aeronutronic, April 1960.)
  145
  Ephemeris of (1580) Betulia. (With T. O. Montgomery.) Minor Planet Circulars 2004, May 9, 1960.
  146
  Ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With T. O. Montgomery.) Minor Planet Circulars 2005, May 26, 1960.
  147
  Positions, velocities, ephemerides referred to the dynamical center. Astrodynamics, Chapter 6. U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report No. 7, July 1960.
  148
  Orbits from position and velocity. Astrodynamics, Chapter 8. U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report No. 8, July 1960.
  149
  Astrodynamical notation and usage. (With Maud W. Makemson and Mary P. Francis.) U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report, No. 10, July 1960.
  150
  Observation requirements for precision orbit determination. Aeronautics and Astronautics, pp. 417-434. (NY-London, Pergamon, 1960.) U.C.L.A. Astronomical Papers, v. 3, No. 4, pp. 23-40.
  151
  Elements and 1961 ten-day ephemerides of (1566) Icarus, (1580) Betulia, and (1620) Geographos. (With T. O. Montgomery.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1961, pp. 42, 43, 146, 154, 157. (Leningrad, 1960.)
  152
  1961 ephemerides of Jupiter's ninth and twelfth satellites. (With Lynn Averill and T. O. Montgomery.) Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v. 73, No. 431, pp. 168-169, April 1961.
  153
  Two-body precision aspects of rendezvous. Lockheed Spacecraft Report, August 1961 (preliminary version); Astrodynamics Research Report, No. 11, Lockheed-California Co. (LR16197), August 1962; U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report No. 15, February 1963.
  154
  The orbits of asteroids and meteors. Proceedings, Lunar and Planetary Exploration Colloquium, v. 2, No. 4, pp. 12-14, November 16, 1961.
  155
  1962 four-day ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With Mary P. Francis.) Minor Planet Circulars 2118-2119, February 20, 1962.
  156
  Space Vehicle Ephemeris and Differential Correction Program Unified Theory. United States Air Force, Air Research and Development Command, Air Force Command and Control Development Division. AFCCDD TN 6034, 496LSPO, June 14, 1960. Aeronutronic Publication U-908.
  157
  Scale and mass in the solar system. Space Age Astronomy, pp. 335-346. (New York-London, Academic Press, 1962.)
  158
  A comparison of astronomical and ballistic traditions in orbit computation. Dynamics of Satellites, pp. 51-64 (ed., Maurice Roy, Berlin-Gottinger-Heidelberg, Springer-Verlag, 1963); U.C.L.A. Astrodynamical Report No. 14, May 1962.
  159
  1580 Betulia. Handbook, British Astronomical Association, 1963, p. 27. November 1962.
  160
  Encke's method using ro, ro as parameters together with both elliptic and universal variables, both for normal integration and for obtaining partial differential coefficients. Section V of analysis of tracking techniques for lunar space vehicles, NASA Interim Technical Report, Contract No. NAS8-2689. (Lockheed-California Co., September 1962.)
  161
  Universal variables, parameters, and equations. (With D. A. Pierce.) Part III of Quarterly Report No. 2 for NASA Contract No. NAS5-2330, pp. 49-60. (Lockheed-California Co., October 1962.)
  162
  Elements and 1963 ten-day ephemeris of 1580 Betulia. (With Mary P. Francis.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1963, pp. 43. 49. (Leningrad, 1962.)
  163
  1963 ttwo-day and four-day ephemeris of 1580 Betulia. (With Mary P. Francis, Lynn Averill, Gun Ohlsson.) Harvard Announcement Card 1580, 1602, January 3, June 7, 1963; Minor Planet Circulars 2165-2166, January 7, 1963.
  164
  Astronomical and "astrodynamical" values of constants and ephemeral data. Bulletin Astronomique, 25, fasc. 1, 105-108, 1965; The System of Astronomical Constants, 95-103 (Paris, Gauthier-Villars, 1965). Preliminary version: Appendix 1, Status Report No. 3, Astrodynamics Constants Analysis, Lockheed LAC/402790, March 1963.
  165
  The fixing of Gaussian gravitational constant and the corresponding geocentric gravitational constant. Bulletin Astronomique, v. 25, fasc. 1, pp. 95-103, 1965; The System of Astronomical Constants, 95-103 (Paris, Gauthier-Villars, 1965). Preliminary version: Appendix 2, Status Report No. 3, Astrodynamics Constants Analysis, Lockheed LAC/402790, March 1963.
  166
  Variation of parameters using ro, ro1, and "universal variables". Section 3.1 of Final Report of NASA Contract No. NAS5-2330, pp. 3.3-1 to 3.14, Lockheed LAC/404845, April 1963.
  167
  Rendezvous and mid-course guidance and control. (Outline lecture notes for University of California Lunar Missions and Exploration Lecture No. 7, April 1-4, 1963.)
  168
  Several formulations of Encke's method. Chapter IV, Analysis of tracking techniques for lunar space vehicles, Interim Technical Report NASA Contract No. NAS8-2689, pp. 4.1 to 4.17, Lockheed LAC/406349, May 1963.
  169
  Introduction to Kalman filter. Chapter V, Analysis of tracking techniques for lunar space vehicles, Interim Technical Report NASA Contract No. NAS8-2689, pp. 5.1-5.17, Lockheed LAC/406349, May 1963.
- SH numbered publications (see also listing in Box 1); numbered publications 170-231 (drafts, correspondence, reprints), 1963-1971. (Box 33)
  170
  The geocentric gravitational constant from radar and angular observations of the Moon. Astrodynamics Research Report No. 17. Lockheed California Co., July 1963.
  171
  Elements and 1964 ten-day ephemeris of 1580 Betulia. (With Mary P. Francis.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1964, pp. 41. 128. (Leningrad, 1963.)
  172
  1965 ten-day ephemeris of 1566 Icarus. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1965, pp. 5, 12, 41, and 140. (Leningrad, 1964.)
  173
  1965 close-approach ephemeris of 1620 Geographos. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1965, pp. 5, 12, 42, and 140. (Leningrad, 1964.) International Astronomical Union Circular 1889-1890, January 22, 1965. (See No. 180.)
  174
  1965 ten-day ephemeris of 1620 Geographos. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1965, pp. 5, 12, 42, and 140. (Leningrad, 1964.)
  175
  Elements, ephemeris, and opposition of 1948 OA. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Minor Planet Circulars 2323, August 1, 1964; Harvard Announcement Card 1651, June 29, 1964.
  176
  1964 ephemeris of 1566 Icarus. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Minor Planet Circulars 2323, August 1, 1964.
  177
  1966 ephemeris of 1566 Icarus. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1966, pp. 5, 102. (Leningrad, 1065.)
  178
  Elements of 1560 Icarus, 1580 Betulia, and 1620 Geographos. Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1966, pp. 41-42. (Leningrad, 1965.)
  179
  1865 ephemeris of 1580 Betulia. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Minor Planet Circulars 2345, February 15, 1965.
  180
  1965 close-approach ephemeris of 1620 Geographos. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Minor Planet Circulars 2345-2346, February 15, 1965. (This ephemeris is an extension of No. 173.)
  181
  1965 close-approach ephemeris of 1948 OA. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Minor Planet Circulars 2346-2347, February 15, 1965. (This ephemeris is an extension of No. 175.)
  182
  1965 ephemeris of 1948 EA. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) International Astronomical Union Circular 1904, April 26, 1965.
  183
  1965 ephemeris of 1566 Icarus. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) International Astronomical Union Circular 1910, June 8, 1965; Minor Planet Circulars 2422, September 4, 1965.
  184
  Universal Variables, Astronomical Journal, 70, No. 4, pp. 309-315, May 1965; cf. errata in Astronomical Journal, 70, No. 6, p. 447, August 1965.
  185
  Single and double integration in the method of variation of parameters. The Theory of Orbits in the Solar System and in Stellar Systems (IAU Symposium #25, Thessalonike, 1964), pp. 274-280. (London-New York, Academic Press, 1966.)
  186
  Elements and residuals of (1685) Toro = 1948 OA. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Minor Planet Circulars 2504, March 10, 1966.
  187
  1966 ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With Robert G. Totten.) International Astronomical Union Circulars 1957 and 1958, May 26, 1966.
  188
  Differential representation in observational differential corrections of orbits. International Astronomical Union Circular Transactions, 12B, pp. 112, 114-115, 1966.
  189
  Improved 1966 ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With Robert G. Totten.) Minor Planet Circulars 2561, June 30, 1966.
  190
  Elements of (1566) Icarus, (1580) Betulia, (1620) Geographos, and (1685) Toro. Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1967, pp. 5, 41, 42, 43. (Leningrad, 1966.)
  191
  1967 ephemeris of (1566) Icarus, (1580) Betulia, and (1685) Toro. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1967, pp. 5, 51, 95, 105, 131. (Leningrad, 1966.)
  192
  Astrodynamic constants analysis. AFCRL-66-129; 128 pp.; prepared for the Air Force Cambridge Research Laboratories, Bedford, Massachusetts. January 31, 1966. Reprinted as: Gravitational, geodetic, and related constants (NAA, SID66-412). Prepublication of portions of Chapters 6 and 18 and Appendex 5 of Astrodynamics.
  193
  Universal Variables. Trajectories of Artificial Celestial Bodies (COSPAR-IAU-IUTAM Symposium, Paris, 1965), 65-67. (Berlin-Heidelberg-New York, Springer-Verlag, 1966.) (Includes addendum to No. 184.)
  194
  Elements of (1566) Icarus, (1580) Betulia, (1620) Geographos, and (1685) Toro, and ephemeris of Icarus. (With Kenneth C. Ford.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1968, pp. 6, 13, 42, 43, 44, and 151. (Leningrad, 1967.)
  195
  1968 ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With P. M. Stevens, IV, E. G. Tezak, P. C. Tiffany, and P. A. Thompson.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2039, October 27, 1967.
  196
  Variations of parameters for trajectory integrations by modern perturbed-variation methods. Proceedings, 18th International Astronautical Congress, (Belgrade 1967, v. 1, 73-85. (Oxford and New York, Pergamon, 1968; Also PWN-Polish Scientific Publishers); U.C.L.A. Astrodynamics Report No. 17, July 1967.
  196A
  See No. 217.
  197
  Close approach ephemeris for (1620) Geographos. (With P. A. Thompson and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2809, 2810. December 15, 1967.
  198
  1968 ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With P. M. Stevens, IV, E. G. Tezak, P. A. Thompson, and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2811, December 15, 1967.
  199
  One-day and two-hour ephemerides of (1566) Icarus. (With R. J. Reichart and P. C. Tiffany.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2065, April 16, 1968.
  200
  Elements of (1566) Icarus, (1580) Betulia, (1620) Geographos, and (1685) Toro, Opposition dates of (1620) Geographos, 10-day ephemeris of (1620) Geographos, and Close Approach Ephemeris of (1620) Geographos. (With P. A. Thompson and P. C. Tiffany.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1969, pp. 5, 8, 44, 45, 46, 55, 57, 153. (Leningrad, 1968.)
  201
  Opposition ephemeris of (1580) Betulia. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2100, September 30, 1968.
  202
  Elements and residuals of (1580) Betulia. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2902, December 15, 1968.
  203
  1968 10-day opposition ephemeris of (1580) Betulia. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2903, December 15, 1968.
  204
  1970 10-day ephemeris of (1580) Betulia. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2903, December 15, 1968.
  205
  Elements and residuals of (1620) Geographos. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2903-2904, December 15, 1968.
  206
  1970 favorable-elongation ephemeris for (1566) Icarus. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2904-2905, December 15, 1968.
  207
  1970 10-day ephemeris of (1685) Toro. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2905, December 15, 1968.
  208
  Elements and residuals of (1685) Toro. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2906, December 15, 1968.
  208A
  See No. 229.
  209
  1969 favorable-elongation ephemeris for (1685) Toro. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2131, February 12, 1969.
  210
  1968-69 ephemerides of JIX and JXII. (With G. E. Newman.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2132, February 12, 1969.
  211
  Close approach ephemeris for (1620) Geographos. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany." International Astronomical Union Circular 2147, May 28, 1969.
  212
  Favorable-elongation ephemeris of (1566) Icarus. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2149, May 40, 1969.
  213
  1969 Favorable-elongation ephemeris for (1566) Icarus. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2964, May 23, 1969.
  214
  Two-day and half-day ephemeris of (1620) Geographos. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 2965, May 23, 1969.
  215
  Continuation of close approach ephemeris for (1620) Geographos. (With P. A. Thompson and P. C. Tiffany.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2171, September 30, 1969. (See No. 197.)
  216
  Elements of (1566) Icarus, (1620) Geographos, (1580) Betulia, and (1685) Toro, Opposition dates for (1580) Betulia and (1685) Toro, Ephemerides of (1685) Toro, (1580) Betulia, and (1566) Icarus. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1970, pp. 5, 11, 40-42, 51, 83, 131, 149. (Leningrad, 1969.)
  217 (196A)
  Techniques for perturbation integration and orbit correction. Herrick Astrondymanics Report under NASA Contract No. NAS5-9706, June 1967. Pre-publication of portions of Chapter 9 and 14 and Appendix 5 of Astrodynamics.
  218
  1969 One-day ephemeris of (1620) Geographos. (With P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 3021, October 1, 1969.
  219
  1970 ephemerides of JIX and JXII. (With G. E. Newnam II.) International Astronomical Union Circular 2211, February 13, 1970.
  220
  Astrodynamics: basic orbital equations. Handbook of Tables for Mathematics, 814-820 (4th ed., S. C. Selby, Cleveland, Chemical Rubber Co., 1970.)
  221
  Astrodynamical terminology, notation, and usage. Handbook of Tables for Mathematics, 821-844 (4th ed., S. C. Selby, Cleveland, Chemical Rubber Co., 1970.)
  222
  Elements of (1566) Icarus, (1620) Geographos, (1580) Betulia, and (1685) Toro, Opposition dates for (1580) Betulia, Favorable-elongation ephemeridies for (1685) Toro, (1566) Icarus, (1620) Geographos. (With R. J. Reichert and P. C. Tiffany.) Ephemerides of Minor Planets, 1971, pp. 6-7, 40-42, 51, 148, 162-163. (Leningrad, 1970.)
  223
  1971 Favorable-elongation ephemeris for (1620) Geographos. (With P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 3105, December 15, 1970.
  224
  1971 10-day opposition ephemeris for (1580) Betulia. (With P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 3105, December 15, 1970.
  225
  1971 Favorable-elongation ephemeris for (1685) Toro. (With P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 3106, December 15, 1970.
  226
  1971 Favorable-elongation ephemeris for (1566) Icarus. (With P. C. Tiffany.) Minor Planet Circulars 3106, December 15, 1970.
  227
  Jupiter IX and XII Ephemerides. (With G. E. Newnam II.) International Astrodynamical Union Circular 2300, January 15, 1971.
  228
  Astrodynamics, Vol. 1: Orbit Determination, Space Navigation, Celestial Mechanics. (London, Van Nostrand Reinhold, 1971) xxvi + 540 pp.
  229